

Applicant for:

Web Backend Developer (Java) ~\$2,000

Dr.JOY 17 April 2020

Toan

Main interests: Java, Spring

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Toan skipped the cover letter.



Full Name: NGUYEN VAN TOAN
Tel Phone: +84356 071 008
Date of birth: 12/02/1991

E-mail: toanbkfet@gmail.com Current Address: Hanoi city, VietNam

Summary

Software Engineer with experience in all levels of testing, software architecture design, analysis functional requirements, coding.

Skill Highlights

Agile/Scrum methodology

Java

- Linux
- PostgreSQL and GridDB database

Language

- Japanese N5
- Can speak or write mail by English in work to communicate with customers

Experience

08/2014 to 06/2017

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Take part in development Network Attached Storage (NAS) for server system:
- Develop kernel on Operating System Debian 6.0.
- Using a most package in order to deploy NAS system such as samba, nfs, pacemake... Using the programming language C and shell script to develop command line for NAS System.
- Test commands line Utility and Replication for server system of vender Toshiba on virtual machine. These virtual machines are Red Hat Enterprise 6.8, 7.2 and Window Server 2012 R2. All the virtual machine installed on VMware ESXi 5.5.
- Take part in test share storage of server system though Brocade Fabric switch. The sever system using Fibre Channel protocol to share storage.
- Deploying ScaleIO v1.32 on ESXi Severs.
- Test Open Stack for server system.

01/2018 to 03/2019

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Designed and implemented the RESTApi (use Spring MVC) for the UI web screen through User Screen the administrator user can assign permisson for each normal user or add/update/delete normal user.
- Test automatic UI web by Selenium

- Know basic knowledge of GitLab (commit code, create merge request to reviewer source code)
- Essential skills are Java 7, Java 8, functional aspects, Spring Framework, Spring Boot, Spring Integration

04/2019 to 09/2019

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Develop Embulk Plugin to transfer data from multiple database (mysql, postgresql...) to GridDB database (use Java language)
- Write script YAML with ANSIBLE for automatic server configuration.
- Develop Kaa Log appenders Plugin for GridDB database (use Java language)
- Test docker build/run dockerfile to automatic install for GridDB database.

04/2020 to 10/2019

Toshiba Software Development VietNam

- Migrate Spring to Spring Boot for backends sever of GridDB database.
- Develop new command line interface use jLine1 plugin for GridDB database. (use Java 8)

Education

Bachelor of Science: Hanoi University of Science and Technology - 2014